verifiedupdates.technology 2015-06-16

# Privacy Policy

##  PRIVACY POLICY

verifiedupdates.technology takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about verifiedupdates.technology's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how verifiedupdates.technology receives, collects and uses information in connection with our website and software provided on the website (the website and software collectively referred to herein as "Site"). 

###  Collection and Use of Information

verifiedupdates.technology does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as names, e-mail, age, gender, address, telephone numbers, login names and passwords or other self-identifying information ("Personal Information"). 

verifiedupdates.technology may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are on verifiedupdates.technology's Site. Cookies may be used to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout as well as for other customer service purposes. verifiedupdates.technology's use of cookies is in no way linked to any Personal Information. 

verifiedupdates.technology may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits. verifiedupdates.technology collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. verifiedupdates.technology will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of its users. 

###  Sharing and Disclosure of Information

verifiedupdates.technology does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties. verifiedupdates.technology may disclose your Personal Information if verifiedupdates.technology believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on verifiedupdates.technology (b) protect and defend the rights or property of verifiedupdates.technology (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of verifiedupdates.technology services or members of the public. 

###  Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to us. We operate our website in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We never knowingly collect or maintain information at or on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 13. Visitors younger than 13 years of age may NOT use the verifiedupdates.technology website and software and must LEAVE immediately. 

###  Explicit Content

You understand that by using the Service, you may encounter content that may be deemed offensive, indecent, or objectionable, which content may or may not be identified as having explicit language. Nevertheless, you agree to use the Site at your sole risk and that verifiedupdates.technology shall have no liability to you for content that may be found to be offensive, indecent, or objectionable. verifiedupdates.technology shall have no liability or responsibility to you for any content or materials that may be available in connection with the Site that you might find objectionable. 

###  Security

verifiedupdates.technology takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although verifiedupdates.technology cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, verifiedupdates.technology has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. Personal Information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. 

###  Changes to Policy

From time to time, verifiedupdates.technology may revise this Policy. verifiedupdates.technology will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information verifiedupdates.technology collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed.
